CURRICULUM VITAE

14 April 2021

Vinh Phuc Le Olympiakatu 12 C1 65100 VAASA

FINLAND

Mobile: +358 46 540 7847

Email: phuclevinh2000@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

RÉSUMÉ PROFILE

I am currently a 3rd year IT student at Vaasa University of Applied Sciences, majoring in Information Technology with a specialization in **Embedded system**. During my study at VAMK have remarkably developed my strong work ethic, communication skills, and enthusiasm in algorithm. Besides, I gain the capability of independent working and handling projects with strict time schedules. At university, I have experienced in *C++*, *C programming language*, *Embedded system design*, *Linux* as well as studies related to the *embedded system*. I also want to learn and be a full stack developer and learn about many frameworks because we are in technology era, and web development technology is modern and attractive to me. So, I try to learn more about web development with *HTML*, *CSS*, *React*, *SASS*, *Bootstrap*, *JavaScript*, *MySQL*. I am interested in new digitalization and would love to learn more about them in the manufacturing field. Regarding languages, I acquire native proficiency in Vietnamese and full professional proficiency in English.

WORK EXPERIENCE

August 2020 - May 2021 FinnBox Oy (Vaasa)

Part-time newspaper distributor

- Deliver daily newspapers at night shift.
- Practice the working under a pressure schedule.

2014 - Aug 2019

K.achi Japanese Restaurant (Vaasa)

Vice chef

- Responsible for cooking main dishes.
- Acquired flexible skills in work and communication.

EDUCATION

Sep 2018 – Now Vaasa University of Applied Sciences, Finland, bachelor's degree

Major: Information Technology, specialized in Embedded system.

SKILLS

React	Made some application with React, Hooks, React Route.
Bootstrap, Flexbox, SASS, Styled- Components	Styled some web application using those Style Sheets
C++ Programming	Familiar with C++ syntax.
C Programming	 Familiar with C syntax Attend to Codeforces programming contests with C language. Work with some projects in C language listed in Project Accomplishment.

 Familiar with the terminal statement as well as Kali Linux. Completed a course related to cyber security at university using Kali Linux.
 Familiar with Arduino, Raspberry Pi, STM32 Nucleo Board, RS232, Learn about RTOS.
 Able to design, print out the design and make a prototype, make it run on breadboard
Design and made a PCB circuit of automatic light,
Design and made some project.
Familiar with basic syntax and still learning
Vietnamese Mother tongueEnglish Fluent

PROJECT ACCOMPLISHMENT

- Made a to-do list application using React.
 Link to the project: https://github.com/phuclevinh2000/Todo_list_app
- Made simple Calculator using React.
 Link to the project: https://github.com/phuclevinh2000/calculator-react
- Made a recipe search application using React.
 Link to the project: https://github.com/phuclevinh2000/Recipe-app
- Made a weather tracker application using React.
 Link to the project: https://github.com/phuclevinh2000/weather-app
- Attended in Coding Competitions (NASA Space App Challenge, Code Abbey, Code Force, Project Euler).
 Link to the project: phuclevinh2000/CodeForce: Codeforce (github.com)
- Build the Sleep tracking application in NASA Space App Challenge 2020. Link to the project: phuclevinh2000/Sleep-Lab (github.com)
- Create an application offer a possibility to turn a Rasberry Pi as a sound device.
 Link to the project: phuclevinh2000/appdev1 (github.com)
- Building and design a receiver and transmitter with PAD Layout and PAD Logic.
- Working on a project to build a slave/master system using Modbus RS-485 and Wapice IoT ticket
 Link to the project: phuclevinh2000/Template-for-STM32: This is a template for STM32 Microcontroller (github.com)
- More technical projects related to programming at my personal GitHub https://github.com/phuclevinh2000.